<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mine Sweeper</string>
    <string name="insane_toast">Insane: 10 x 80 with 160 mine</string>
    <string name="hard_toast">Hard: 10 x 40 with 40 mines</string>
    <string name="medium_toast">Medium: 10 x 20 with 20 mines</string>
    <string name="easy_toast">Easy: 10 x 10 with 10 mines</string>
    <string name="mines_toast">The amount of mines left. But who knows if you placed your flags correctly...</string>
    <string name="timer_toast">The clock is ticking! Hurry up, this is how you will be ranked!</string>
    <string name="too_many_flags_toast">You have already flagged all supposed mines. Questioning yourself now, are you?</string>
    <string name="leaderboard_info">This is the leader board. You can create new users here. Press a user to switch to that profile. Long press to delete that user.</string>
    <string name="win_message_no_record">You flagged all the mines! Unfortunately you did not beat your record. Keep trying!</string>
    <string name="about_dialog"><![CDATA[Hello! My name is Kevin Hodges. 10 months ago I was a firefighter, and now I\'m a full fledged Android developer. I needed a new career and I found it in Android development, I\'ve absolutely loved my time with it. There is nothing better than creating something out of nothing, and that\'s what I am able to do with Android. At this point I have created 5 apps and I am currently in the middle of a large, text based adventure game. All of my apps make great use of material design guidelines and are very appealing to the eyes. I have learned an absolute ton in 10 months and I am ready to join a team to learn from the best and also offer what I can. This application was created for a JP Morgan & Chase code assessment. It incorporates all of the tried and true Mine Sweeper game play that you have grown to love, with a new, polished, material design look. I made the decision to go with a consistent 10 column layout for the game board regardless of the game board difficulty chosen. This is not how the typical game is presented, but I felt this allowed much easier mobile oriented/one handed game play which adds to the experience. I implemented a high score system instead of the old \'low time\' design. I basically reward a certain amount of points based on each difficulty, then subtract 10 points per second until the puzzle is finished. I also decided to go with a \'flag all mines\' win condition. The typical Mine Sweeper would have you guess towards the end of the game, which could result in a loss. I simply just require the user to flag all mines to win. You still have to know what you are doing to win, but it does alleviate some of the frustration that the guessing scenario can create. I hope you enjoy my version of this classic. Please leave some feedback on Google Play. Thanks!]]></string>
</resources>
